<sections title="New Features" emphasize_first="Older...">
    <section title="March 8, 2012" linktitle="20120308">
        <item>
            <title>
                Resistances, Themes, Weight Carried, and Height/Weight
            </title>
            <content>
                A prominent display of Resistances right below Hit Points and damage means you'll never
                again forget to substract your resistances from damage.  iPlay4e helps keep your character alive!
                Also new to the sheet are Themes, Weight Carried, and Height/Weight (using defaults for your
                race if you never specified them).
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Backup Players / Co-DMs
            </title>
            <content>
                The DM may set a new campaign option that allows players to modify each other's characters - because
                sometimes, not everyone can make every session.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Flexible die roller
            </title>
            <content>
                The updated die roller on the full-screen sheet lets you roll arbitrary dice like 3d8+5.
            </content>
        </item>
    </section>
    <section title="February 5, 2012" linktitle="20120205">
        <item>
            <title>
                Power Point tracking
            </title>
            <content>
                You can now track your character's power points in both the full screen and mobile interfaces.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Improved Death Saves visibility
            </title>
            <content>
                If your character's current Death Saves are below 3, they are now displayed even if your
                character is conscious.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Bugfixes
            </title>
            <content>
                Lock icon now accurately indicates character and campaign visibility, XP transfer across Character Builder and iPlay4e fixed.
            </content>
        </item>
    </section>
    <section title="June 30, 2011" linktitle="20110630">
        <item>
            <title> 
                Customizable Power Cards
            </title>
            <content>
                Thanks to changes in WotC's <i>dnd4e</i> format, character sheets now have
                complete power card information.  Editable notes let you customize the
                card for every power, skill, feat, and item on your sheet.  Attack rollers
                let you specify the number of targets.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title> 
                Group play with iPad or other tablets
            </title>
            <content>
                The new character sheet offers improved behavior on tablet devices,
                and instant character switching makes device sharing possible.
                Pass a tablet or two around the gaming table.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title> 
                inCombat live syncing
            </title>
            <content>
                Andrew Siefer's excellent inCombat tracker can now receive live hit point
                updates from iPlay4e characters, enabling easy networked play.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title> 
                Improved character sheet
            </title>
            <content>
                The new layout makes it even easier to play your character by focusing
                on the things you use most frequently and reducing visual clutter.
            </content>
        </item>
    </section>
    <section title="May 14, 2010" linktitle="20100514">
        <item>
            <title> 
                Native Android browser support
            </title>
            <content>
                Thanks to the efforts of
                <a target="brindy" href="http://www.brindy.org.uk/"><u>Christopher Brindy</u></a>,
                iPlay4e now works in the native Android browser.  He worked some Java/GoogleAppEngine/XSL-fu
                that lets us get around the Android's XSL limitations by using a back-end service he wrote.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title> 
                Embedded combat tracking
            </title>
            <content>
                Andrew Siefer's excellent inCombat tracker is now embedded right into iPlay4e,
                with all of the public characters in the campaign preloaded!  Campaign owners
                should check out the new "Fight using inCombat" tab.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title> 
                Money editing
            </title>
            <content>
                You can now add and subtract coins from both your carried and stored money.
                When you download your <i>dnd4e</i> file, your changes are retained.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title> 
                DM mode
            </title>
            <content>
                The owner of a campaign (usually the DM) can now track all of the characters in the campaign.  
                This includes hit points, experience points, money, and everything else the player can track.
                Upload of replacement <i>dnd4e</i> files is still limited to the owner of the character.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title> 
                Improved navigation tabs
            </title>
            <content>
                The full-screen view now puts all tabs across a single row for even quicker access to 
                everything on your sheet.
            </content>
        </item>
    </section>
    <section title="March 12, 2010" linktitle="20100312">
        <item>
            <title> 
                Combat tracking
            </title>
            <content>
                Andrew Siefer's excellent inCombat tracker can now be accessed from your
                campaign's new Fight menu.  It reads in the entire party at once!
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title> 
                Campaign planning
            </title>
            <content>
                Andy Aiken's wonderful Masterplan product is now integrated with iPlay4e.
                Your character key (available in the Link/Embed menu) can be entered right into his
                lovely product, which is available 
                <a target="masterplan" href="http://www.habitualindolence.net/masterplan/"><u>here</u></a>.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title> 
                Printable character sheets
            </title>
            <content>
                Beautiful, full-color sheets can now be created using Shado's Sheet Generator by Andrew Siefer.
                Available in your character's File menu.
            </content>
        </item>
    </section>
    <section title="January 31, 2010" linktitle="20100131">
        <item>
            <title> 
                Campaign Management
            </title>
            <content>
                Campaigns group together players and characters for sharing and easy reference.  
                All it takes to create one is a name and an optional campaign world.  
                Once you have a campaign, you can add other players by entering their Google email address or their iPlay4e handle.
                You and the other players can add your characters to the campaign, where they are all visible at once - 
                    including status like current hit points and power usage.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title> 
                Browser Interface Redesign
            </title>
            <content>
                There's a whole new look and feel for iPlay4e on the desktop.  
                The full-screen character sheet has been refreshed, and is no longer hidden behind an obscure icon.
                Characters are stacked vertically to avoid side-to-side scrolling, 
                    and default to a combat bar view that lets you monitor the health of several characters at once.  
                The View menu lets you expand them all or open each in a separate window.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title> 
                Full Text Search
            </title>
            <content>
                The search feature has been changed to return characters and campaigns based on what you type.
                Need a level 7 defender for a guest player?  Search for "defender 7".
                Want to see all paragon tier fighters?  Search for "fighter 11-20".
                Want to see all of the campaigns in your favorite setting?  Search for "forgotten".
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title> 
                More Mobile Functionality
            </title>
            <content>
                All of the site's features, including characters, campaigns, and search, are now available on your mobile device.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title> 
                Optimized Tablet Interface
            </title>
            <content>
                A variation on the full-screen sheet, this interface is optimized for use on tablets.
                Now you know why Apple developed the iPad - to be the coolest character sheet that ever existed!
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title> 
                User Handles
            </title>
            <content>
                Use the new Settings menu to specify a unique handle for yourself on iPlay4e.  
                Your handle will appear in the campaigns you join, and others may use your handle to invite you to new campaigns.
                Perfect for setting up play-by-post games where you might not want to post your email address to a forum.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title> 
                Google Wave and other Embedding Features
            </title>
            <content>
                You're already able to embed your character 
                    on your web site, on Epic Words, or as a gadget in Google Wave, Google Desktop, and iGoogle.
                Now you can embed your campaigns as well!
            </content>
        </item>
    </section>
    <section title="July 15, 2009" linktitle="20090715">
        <item linktitle="upload">
            <title> 
                Full screen character sheets
            </title>
            <content>
                With a built-in <b>D&amp;Di Compendium</b> browser, our new full screen character sheets
                are better than power cards.
                The new icon, found next to the red pushpin, opens your character in full-screen mode
                for laptop or desktop play.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                More mobile device support
            </title>
            <content>
                including <b>Blackberry</b>, <b>T-Mobile G1</b>, other <b>Android</b> phones and all other devices
                that can run the Opera Mini mobile web browser.
            </content>
        </item>
    </section>
    <section title="June 17, 2009" linktitle="20090617">
        <item>
            <title>
                Improved user interface
            </title>
            <content>
                ensures that no piece of character information is more than two clicks or touches away.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Google Gadgets compatability
            </title>
            <content>
                lets you put your character right on your Google home page or Google Desktop.
                The new Google Gadget link is found in the Star Menu.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Forums export
            </title>
            <content>
                New options in the Star Menu allow you to export your character to the D&amp;Di forums, 
                Something Awful play-by-post and other forums.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Active embedding
            </title>
            <content>
                Characters embedded on other pages (including Google) can be played from those pages.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                XP tracking
            </title>
            <content>
                You can now add XP to your character at the end of session, so you only need to download
                your character when you level up or get significant gear.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Friendly IP4XML format
            </title>
            <content>
                Characters can now be loaded in both standard <i>dnd4e</i> and third-party-friendly <i>ip4xml</i> formats.
                Build your own XSL character sheets using our XML format; you can even use the full screen
                and mobile interfaces as starting points.
            </content>
        </item>
    </section>
    <section title="April 28, 2009" linktitle="20090428">
        <item>
            <title>
                Character Builder update compatability
            </title>
            <content>
                The April 28 release of the Character Builder changed the dnd4e save file format.
                The iPlay4e application supports both the old and new formats.  Thanks to the WotC team
                for these changes, described in greater detail below.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Epic Words campaign wiki integration
            </title>
            <content>
                We are pleased to announce our first collaboration with a third party campaign manager:
                    <a target="epicwords" href="http://epicwords.com">Epic Words</a>.
                Just click the "Embed" link in your character's start menu to get wiki code for embedding
                your character on any Epic Words wiki page, or to get your character key for providing when
                configuring your character on that site.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Turn planning
            </title>
            <content>
                The new Character Builder format includes each power's action type (standard, move, minor, etc...),
                which has allowed us to provide icons on the main screen that lists all your powers.  Plan your turn
                at a glance, or drill into your powers for details!
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Improved calculation accuracy
            </title>
            <content>
                The new Character Builder format also provides attack and damage calculations for each legal
                combination of power and weapon.  The iplay4e site leverages these calculations, and no longer
                has to figure it out on its own.  This should eliminate a whole category of bugs, and automatically
                account for new feats and other bonuses as they become supported by the Character Builder.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Conditional bonuses
            </title>
            <content>
                With some powers, weapons, or feats, there are bonuses that are not always applied to your
                attack and damage rolls.  The new format lists these, and so does iplay4e.
            </content>
        </item>
    </section>
    <section title="April 16, 2009" linktitle="20090416">
        <item>
            <title>
                Dice Rollers
            </title>
            <content>
                Digital dice for initiative, skill checks, ability checks, attack rolls, and damage rolls 
                (and a vanilla roller in case we missed something).
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Complete character tracking
            </title>
            <content>
                Character tracking now includes temporary hit points, death saves, and magic item consumption,
                providing all missing features from the first tracker release.
            </content>
        </item>
    </section>
    <section title="April 10, 2009" linktitle="20090410">
        <item>
            <title>
                Announcing iplay4e labs
            </title>
            <content>
                Point your browser at <a target="_top" href="http://labs.iplay4e.com">labs.iplay4e.com</a> for
                a preview of features that will soon be added to iplay4e.  
                This lets our more daring users try out new features, and helps us iron out the wrinkles
                before we deploy those features to the main site.  <br /><br />Currently in the lab:
                <ul style="padding-left:6px;">
                    <li> Built in dice roller for all attack powers! </li>
                    <li> Improved character tracking, including temporary hit points, death save, and magic item use consumption. </li>
                </ul>
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Forum updates
            </title>
            <content>
                You can now see the latest posts to the iplay4e forum without even leaving the site.
                In addition, we have consolidated the main forum and the bugs forum to make things simpler.
            </content>
        </item>
    </section>
    <section title="March 19, 2009" linktitle="20090319">
        <item>
            <title>
                Character tracking
            </title>
            <content>
                For characters you own, it is now possible to track hit points, conditions,
                healing surges, action points, and power consumption.  Still in progress:
                death saves, magic item consumption, and temporary hit points.
            </content>
        </item>
    </section>
    <section title="February 27, 2009" linktitle="20090227">
        <item>
            <title>
                Character embedding
            </title>
            <content>
                The outlet icon visible by any public character provides instructions
                for embedding that character on any web site.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Compendium compatibility update
            </title>
            <content>
                Works with the new version of the DDI Compendium release on March 25th.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Navigation improvements
            </title>
            <content>
                Browsing your characters, shared characters, and searching are now simpler.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Bug fixes...
            </title>
            <content>
                <ul style="padding-left:6px;">
                    <li>Magic items not included on Gear panel.</li>
                    <li>Magic item bonuses not included in power panels.</li>
                    <li>Rogue weapon bonus not calculated in power panels.</li>
                    <li>Charisma score not visible on iPhone or in Safari.</li>
                    <li>Unicode characters (umlauts, accents, etc...) in names blocked character upload.</li>
                </ul>
            </content>
        </item>
    </section>
    <section title="February 17, 2009" linktitle="20090217">
        <item>
            <title>
                Character search
            </title>
            <content>
                You can now search for characters by level, race, class, role, and power source.
            </content>
        </item>
    </section>
    <section title="February 13, 2009" linktitle="20090213">
        <item>
            <title>
                Character file download
            </title>
            <content>
                The file icon displayed next to each character name allows you to download their
                dnd4e file for use with the character builder.
            </content>
        </item>
    </section>
    <section title="February 12, 2009" linktitle="20090212">
        <item>
            <title>
                Character sharing
            </title>
            <content>
                Click the lock icon after browsing a character to share it with specific people.
                If your gaming group shares their characters with your game master, the
                game master can build a quick reference page including the entire party.
            </content>
        </item>
    </section>
</sections>
