<sections title="Help and FAQ" TOC="TOC">
    <section title="Search" linktitle="search">
        <item>
            <title>How do I use the iPlay4e search feature?</title>
            <content>
                Enter search terms into the search box near the top of the page.
                Then press Enter on your keyboard or the Search button with your mouse.
                The site will display the public characters and campaigns that match the search terms you entered.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>What kind of search terms can I use?</title>
            <content>
                Characters are searchable by level, name, race, class, build, power source, and role.
                Campaigns are searchable by name, setting, description, player, and character.
                You can also combine search terms to narrow the results further.  Here
                are some examples:
                <ul>
                    <li><i>gilpa</i> finds the character named Gilpa, and any campaigns Gilpa is in.</li>
                    <li><i>5</i> finds all 5th level characters.</li>
                    <li><i>defender 5</i> finds all 5th level characters with the defender role.</li>
                    <li><i>eladrin</i> finds all characters of the eladrin race.</li>
                    <li><i>swordmage</i> finds all characters of the swordmage class.</li>
                    <li><i>assault swordmage</i> finds all characters with the assault swordmage build.</li>
                    <li><i>arcane defender</i> finds all characters with the arcane power source and the defender role.</li>
                </ul>
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Can I search for a range of levels?</title>
            <content>
                To search for all characters in a given range, just enter the lowest
                and highest levels you are interested in separated by a dash (no spaces).
                To find all paragon tier arcane characters, you would search for <i>arcane 11-20</i>.
            </content>
        </item>
    </section>
    <section title="Character Management and Tracking" linktitle="management">
        <item linktitle="upload">
            <title>How do I upload a new character?</title>
            <content>
                Click the <i>New</i> link near the upper right corner of the screen, then the Character link.
                A small window will open, with a button you can press for selecting a file.
                Select a file, adjust the checkboxes if you like, then press the Upload button.
                In a few seconds, your character will be ready to be played.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>What sort of files should I upload?</title>
            <content>
                The site uses <i>dnd4e</i> files generated by the Character Builder.  These
                will typically be found in the "ddi\Saved Characters" directory of My Documents. 
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>What's the best way to make sure that iPlay4e and Character Builder stay in sync?</title>
            <content>
                It's best to think of iPlay4e as the "home location" of your character.  When you want
                to make changes in Character Builder, use the download option in the file menu.  When
                prompted whether to open or save the file, open it using the Character Builder application.
                When you're done making changes, save the file file to an easy-to-find location, such as
                your Desktop, then immediately upload it to iPlay4e.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>How do I upload a replacement file for an existing character?</title>
            <content>
                Open the File menu next to your character's name, then click the "Upload replacement dnd4e file" link.
                Select the replacement file.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>What should I do when I level up?</title>
            <content>
                Download your .dnd4e file using the character's File menu, then open it in Character Builder.
                Level up using the Character Builder and save the .dnd4e file.  Upload it as a replacement file
                using your character's File menu.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>
                Just how random is your random number generator? 
                I just got a bunch of low rolls in a row.  
                Why does <i>iPlay4e</i> hate me?
            </title>
            <content>
                Pretty darn random.  We use an algorithm better than the built-in Javascript Math.random() function.
                Runs of high and low values are to be expected from true randomness.  If the number distribution didn't 
                have the occasional "lump" one would be suspicious.  Dice will do the same thing.  If you're not yet
                convinced, <a href="#" onclick="$('randomProof').show();return false;"><u>look at this graph of results</u></a> 
                generated using our algorithm:
                <br/>
                <img id="randomProof" src="/TIME_TOKEN/images/random.png" style="display:none;" />
                <br/>
                Looks an awful lot like white noise, right?  You see, <i>iPlay4e</i> loves you!
            </content>
        </item>
    </section>
    <section title="Troubleshooting and Feedback" linktitle="troubleshooting">
        <item>
            <title> What browsers do you support?  I'm seeing some strange behavior...  </title>
            <content>
                The site is tested on:
                <ul>
                    <li>Internet Explorer 7 and 8</li>
                    <li>Firefox 3</li>
                    <li>Google Chrome</li>
                    <li>Safari 4</li>
                    <li>Safari Mobile (iPhone and iPod Touch)</li>
                    <li>Opera Mini (Blackberry, G1, Android, most smartphones)</li>
                    <li>Palm Pre (or so we hear, but not having one we can't test for ourselves)</li>
                </ul>
                If you're using a different browser, we can give no guarantees.  
                <br/><br/>
                In the listed browsers, up to nine characters can safely belong to any given campaign.
                More than that may be trouble in Safari and Safari Mobile.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item linktitle="badgoodlinks">
            <title>The Compendium is broken for one of my powers, or I'm being asked if it's good.</title>
            <content>
                Occasionally, a bad link slips through both the Character Builder and iPlay4e.  We have
                a system in place that lets you help us determine whether a link is good or bad.  When we
                come across one that hasn't been reviewed before, we'll ask you whether it's good or bad.
                If you're seeing a compendium login screen, please sign in before deciding whether the
                ink is bad or good. A bad link will show an error like "Server Error in / Application".
                A good link will show you the description of the power from the compendium.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title> Help! Something else is broken, and it's not my browser!</title>
            <content>
                Please 
                <a target="forumWin" href="http://groups.google.com/group/iplay4e/post?subject=BUG">post on the <i>iplay4e</i> forums</a>.
                Include a description of how we can reproduce the issue, and attach your <i>dnd4e</i> file
                if it's a problem with a specific character.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title> How do I make a feature suggestion?  </title>
            <content>
                We'd love to hear from you about how we can make <i>iplay4e</i> more useful to you.
                First, you should 
                <a target="roadmap" href="http://code.google.com/p/iplay4e/issues/list?can=2&amp;q=&amp;colspec=ID+Type+Status+Priority+Milestone+Source+Owner+Summary+Description&amp;sort=&amp;x=priority&amp;y=type&amp;cells=tiles&amp;mode=grid">check the product roadmap</a> to make sure it's not already on our schedule.  If it's not, just 
                <a target="forumWin" href="http://groups.google.com/group/iplay4e/post?subject=SUGGESTION">post your request to 
                    the <i>iplay4e</i> forums</a>.
            </content>
        </item>
    </section>
    <section title="Policies" linktitle="policies">
        <item>
            <title> Can I post from someone else's material here?  </title>
            <content>
                We strongly suggest that you do not, but should you do so, 
                make sure that the character or campaign is classified as <i>private</i>.<br /><br />
                <i>Do not duplicate copyrighted material as a public item on this site.</i>
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title> How do I make a character or campaign private, then?  </title>
            <content>
                Use the "Share" menu that appears to the right of the item's name.
            </content>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title> What do I do if I see a character on the site that looks like it's from published material?  </title>
            <content>
                <a href="mailto://legal@iplay4e.com">Narc to the <i>iplay4e</i> administrators</a>.
            </content>
        </item>
    </section>
</sections>
